there's a lot of surprises, other than the reference to the PCSK9 outcomes trials. So I think
we're trying to understand that, you know, given that usually we don't get to refer to somebody
else's outcome studies. And I think with respect to the, other than that, nothing that changes our
view. I mean, look, our belief is that there's a significant segment of the market, and this is a
huge market, and the number of patients who are not at goal.
For lipid lowering to reach their lipid targets is significant in the United States. You know,
we're talking about here a 70 million patient segment overall, you know, a significant portion
of these patients who are not at goal. And so I think the opportunity for the PCSK9s is,
for these advanced lipid lowering therapies is significant. And we see that there's ongoing
demand for patients who want infrequently administered therapies and physicians who
want to provide the therapy as well.
In the physician-administered setting. So I think the fact that we're not participating
in the gross-to-net battle that will ensue between the monoclonal antibodies and the orals
actually are in a segment that's insulated from that, I think is a strong position in the longer
run for our goals of a $4 billion to $5 billion plus product. Now, with respect to the food effect,
I think it remains to be seen. I mean, I think clearly the eight-hour fast plus the
30, I think it's a 30-minute or so post-fast in this particular drug. But, you know, I think
we'll have to see because obviously patients can find ways to manage that. And I would say there
are other competitors coming that, as far as we understand, may not have the food effect. So
given that, I think we just have to focus on our segment and focus on the patients that we can
reach in that Part B buy-and-bill setting in the U.S. I do want to pitch again outside of the U.S.,
particularly in the U.S.
In Asia, we see very strong uptake for SIRNAs. And we think that in some, it's a very country-by-country
situation as to, you know, what kind of profile people are looking for in the medicines. And at
least in Asia and Middle East, we see a high demand for SIRNAs. It gives us a lot of confidence.
Thank you.
Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of Sachin Jain from Bank of America. Please go
ahead.
Hi, thanks for the follow-up. I just had a one.
Hi, Sachin.